Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Laurent, Happy, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lavin, David, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lawyers Committee on Nuclear Policy, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Le Comte, Edward, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Leahy, Patrick, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Lear, Martha, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Lear, Norman, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Lear's, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Lederer, Michel, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Lee, Shirley Thurston, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Lees, Dick, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Leggett, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Legiardi-Laura, Roland, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Lehigh University, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Lehmann-Haupt, Christopher, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Leibovitz, Maury, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Leigh Bureau, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - [re:] Leigh, Candace, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Leigh, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Leitenburg, Milton, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Lelchuk, Alan, undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Leonardo Editore, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Lerner, Linda, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Levertov, Denise, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Levine, Elizabeth, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Levine, Laura, undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Levine, Paul, undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Levine, Philip, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Levinson, Sanford, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Levita, Ruth, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Levitin, Martin, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Levy, Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Levy, Harold, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Levy, Leonard, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Levy, Martin, undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Levy, Phyllis, undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Lewin, Leonard, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Lewin, Michael, undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Lewis, David, undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Lewis, Harry, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Lewis, Willee, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Lews, Rosemary, undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Liberation, undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Libin, Paul, undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Libraries for the Future, undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Liebmann, Lisa, undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Life, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Lifton, Robert Jay, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Limerick, University of-, undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Lipke, Alan, undated (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Lipper, Kenneth, undated (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Lippincott Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Lipton, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Lish, Gordon, undated (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Litchfield Associates, undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Literary Partners, Inc., undated (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Literal Latte, undated (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Literary Criticism Series, undated (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - The Literary Network, undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Literacy Volunteers of America, undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Little, Brown, & Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Little Red School House, undated (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Livent (producers of the musical version of Ragtime), undated (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Livent (producers of the musical version of Ragtime), undated (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Livent (from Doctorow), undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Livent (from Doctorow), undated (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Lloyd, Amy, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - LM Magazine, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Loft, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - London, Ephraim, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Jack London Foundation, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - London Review of Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Long Island University, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lopez-Chicheri, Eduardo Garrigues, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lord, Pamela, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lord, Sterling, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lorsh, Susan, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles County Public Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles Times, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lottman, Eileen and Evan, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - The Lotus Club, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Louisiana Public Broadcasting, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Louisiana State University, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Louisville, University of-, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Love, Kennett, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Lowell Enterprises, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Loyola Marymount University, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lubarsky, Jared, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Luers, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lukic, Darko, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lumet, Sidney, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Luzader, Susan, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Lynch, Dennis, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Lynch, Warren, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Lynds, Dennis, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Lynn C. Franklin Associates, Ltd., undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - "Ma", undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - "Mb-Mon", undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "Moo-Mz", undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Maas, Peter, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - MacArthur Foundation, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - McCaffrey, Larry, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - McClelland & Stewart, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - McConnell, Joseph, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - McCullough, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - [re:] Macdonald, Cynthia, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - MacDowell Colony, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Mcduff, Laurence, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - McGill University, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - McGinniss, Joe, undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Co., undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Machlis, Joseph, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - McKay, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Maclean, A. D., undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Macmillan, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Macmillan, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - MacNeil-Lehrer-Gannet Productions, undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - McQuade, Molly, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - John Macrae Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Mad Magazine, undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Madison College, undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Madoo Conservancy, undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Madre, undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Mahon, Derek, undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Mailer, Norman, undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Main Stage Theatre Guild, undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Maine Audubon Society, undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Mamet, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Manas, undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - The Manhattan Playhouse, undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Manhattanville College, undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - il Manifesto, undated (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Elena Mannes Productions, undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Manoa, undated (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Mansfield State College, undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Manuscript Appeal, undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Marcus, Bobbi, undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Markman, Claire, undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Marin, College of-, undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Marmor, Joan, undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Marmur, Mildred, undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Marranca, Richard, undated (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Martin, Don, undated (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Martin, Jo Nobuko, undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Martins Ferry Public Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Marxist Perspectives, undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Maryland, College Park, University of-, undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Maso, Carole, undated (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Massachusetts Arts and Humanities Foundation, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Massachusetts College of Art, undated (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, undated (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Massie, Robert K., undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Masters, Hilary, undated (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Match, Ronald, undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Mather, Jeff, undated (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Mather-Thrift, Marsha, undated (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Mattes, Joseph, undated (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Matthiessen, Peter, undated (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Mattituck Free Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Mayfield, Suellen, undated (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Mazie, Lowell, undated (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Medem Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Medical Aid for El Salvador, undated (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Mediums, undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Meerapal, Mike, undated (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Meglin, Nick, undated (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Mehta, Gita and Sonny, undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Meissner, Bill, undated (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Mekas, Adolfas, undated (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Melbourne Spoleto Writers' Festival, undated (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Mellen, Joan, undated (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, undated (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Memories, undated (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Memphis State University, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Mennel, Timothy, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Men's Journal, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Mental Health Association of Prince George's County, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - The Mercantile Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Mercy College, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Merkin Concert Hall, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Il Messaggero, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Messinger, Ruth, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Methuen, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Metzenbaum, Howard, undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Meyer, Howard, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Mezey, Bob, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mezey, Phiz, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Mezzy, Marin, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miami Book Fair International, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miami Herald, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Miami University, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Michael, James, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Michael Joseph, Ltd., undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Michigan State University, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Michigan, University of-, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Middlebury College, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Middle Island Central Schools, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Miles, Lisa, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Arnie, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Bernie and Anita, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Miller, Judy, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Millsaps College, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Milton, Peter, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Milwaukee Writers Project, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Minkoff, George Robert, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Minnesota, University of-, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Minnich, Elizabeth, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Mirabella, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Miramax Books, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Mishkenot Sha'ananim Guest House, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Missouri, University of-, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Mitchell, Brian Stokes, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Mitchell, George, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Mitgang, Herbert, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Modern Library, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Moffitt, Keats & Jones, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Molitor, Ulrike, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Moment, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Monacelli Press, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Mondadori Publishing Co., undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Monmouth County Library, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Monroe County Library System, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Montana, University of-, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Monthly Review Foundation, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Moody, Anne, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Moody, Vearl, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Moore, Harold, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Moore, Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - More, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Morell, Jamie, undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Moret, Ramón G. Rivera, undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Morgan, Arthur, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - The Morgan Library, undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Morgan, Beth, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Morgan, Michael Hamilton, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Moritz, Arthur, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Morningstar Productions, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Morrell & Co., undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Morris, County College of-, undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Morris, Mary, undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Morris, Christopher (Topper), undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Morrison, Toni, undated (Box 13, Folder 57a.)
  - William Morrow & Co., undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Mosaic, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Mosher, Stephen, undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Moskin, Bob, undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Mother Jones, undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Motion Picture Association of America, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Mount Holyoke College, undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Mount Saint Vincent, College of-, undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - A Moveable Feast, undated (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Moyers, Bill, undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Moyniham, Daniel Patrick, undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - MPA (Magazine Publishers of America) / ASME (American Society of Magazine Editors), undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Muchnik Editores, undated (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Mueller, Lavonne, undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Muney, Brian, undated (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Municipal Art Society of New York, undated (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Murder Ink, undated (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Murphy, William and Barbara, undated (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Museum of the City of New York, undated (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Muske, Carol, undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - "N", undated (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - NAACP, undated (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Nadis, Fred, undated (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Nagyvilag, undated (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Nassau Community College, undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Nathans, Rhoda, undated (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - The Nation, undated (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - The Nation, undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - The Nation, undated (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - National Academy of Design, undated (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - The National Arts Club, undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - National Arts Journalism Program, undated (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - National Book Critics Circle, undated (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - National Book Foundation, undated (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - National Central America Health Rights Network, undated (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - National Coalition Against Censorship, undated (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - National Committee to Reopen Rosenberg Case, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - National Dance Institute, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - National Forum (Honor Society of Phi Kappa Phi), undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - National Humanities Center, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - National Jewish Welfare Board, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - National Museum of American Jewish History, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - National Public Radio, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - National Theatre Workshop of the Handicapped, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - National Writers Club, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - National Writers Union, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - National Writers Voice Project, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Native American Rights Fund, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The Nature Conservancy, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Navasky, Victor, undated (Box 14, Folder 17a.)
  - NBC, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Nebraska Public Television, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Nederlandse Christelijke Radio Vereniging (NCRV), undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Neumeyer, Peter, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Nevler, Leona, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - New American Library, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - New Directions, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - New England Review, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - New 42nd Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - The New Group, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - New Orleans Writers' Conference, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - New Party, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - New Perspectives Quarterly, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - The New Press, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - New Republic, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - New Rochelle, City of-, undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - New Rochelle, College of-, undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - New Rochelle High School, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - New Rochelle Public Library, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New School for Social Research, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New Shakespeare Company, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New York Archives Week, undated (Box 14, Folder 38a.)
  - New York Book Fair, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - New York Botanical Garden, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New York City 100, undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New York Council for the Humanities, undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - New York Historical Society, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - New York Herald Tribune, undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - New York Institute for the Humanities, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - New York Kid's Catalog, undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - New York Landmarks Conservatory, undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - New York Library Association, undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - New York Magazine, undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - New York Medical College, undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - New York Newsday, undated (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - New York Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign, undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - New York, Parks and Recreation, City of-, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - New York Post, undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group, Inc., undated (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - New York Public Library, undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - New York Public Library, undated (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - New York Society for Ethical Culture, undated (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - New York State Common Cause, undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - New York State English Council, undated (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - New York State Historical Records / Documentary Heritage Program, undated (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - New York State Writers Institute, undated (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - New York Stock Exchange, undated (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - New York Theological Seminary, undated (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - New York Times, undated (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - New York University, undated (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - New York University, undated (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - New York University, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The New Yorker, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Newberger, Greenberg, and Associates, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - NewHarvest, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Newlove, Don, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Newman, Paul, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Newmarket Press, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Newsday, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Nichols, Mike and Annabel, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Neiman Foundation, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Night of 100 Stars, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Nimrod, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 939 Foundation for the Arts, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Nobel Committee of the Swedish Academy, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Norstedts, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - North American Congress on Latin American, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - North Carolina, Chapel Hill, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - North Carolina, Charlotte, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - North Carolina, Greensboro, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - North Castle Public Library, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - North Dakota, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Northshire Bookstore, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - North Star Fund, Inc., undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - North Stone Review, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - North Texas, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Northeastern Illinois University, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Northeastern University, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Northern Ohio Live, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Northwestern University, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Northwest Missouri State University, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Norton, Peter, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - W. W. Norton & Co., undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Notre Dame, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Nouveau, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - le Nouvel Observateur, undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Novel & Short Story Writer's Market, undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Nuland, Sherwin, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - "O", undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Oakwood School, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol / Smith, Ray, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Oberlin College, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - O'Brien, Michael James, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - The Observer, undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Oceanside Free Library, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Oderman, Stuart, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Ogden, Robert, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Ohio University, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Ohio University, Belmont, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Ohnesorge-Fick, Karen, undated (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Oklahoma, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Old Foyle College, undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Olds, Sharon, undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Olsen, Betty Weiss, undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - The Olsen House, undated (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Omero / Pietro Pedace, undated (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Omni Publications, undated (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Omnibus, undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline, undated (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - One City Cafe, undated (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - O'Neill, William, undated (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Ono, Yoko, undated (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Open Call, undated (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Oracle Press, undated (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Oregon, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Organization of American Historians, undated (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Orkin, Jenna, undated (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Orlock, Carol, undated (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Oslo, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Ossabaw, Edwin, undated (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Ottawa, University of-, undated (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Outlet, Book Company, Inc., undated (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - The Overlook Press, undated (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Owaton, Annie, undated (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Oxford University Press, undated (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Oxnard, Katherine, undated (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - "P", undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pacchiana, Jeanne and Doug, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pace University, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pacific Lutheran University, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Pacifica Graduate Institute, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Packard, James, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Paley, Grace, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pallas, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Panache, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Pan Books, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Panorama Magazine, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Pantheon Books, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Papaleo, Joseph, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Paperbacks Plus, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)